var words = 
[
    {
        "question": "لِآدَمَ",
        "answer": "to Adam",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "liādama",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "آدَمَ",
        "answer": "(the) children of Adam",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "ādama",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِبْلِيسَ",
        "answer": "Iblis",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ib'līsa",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَبَىٰ",
        "answer": "but refused",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "fa-abā",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَبَى",
        "answer": "But refused",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "fa-abā",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْتُوا",
        "answer": "bring",
        "pcklId": "124",
        "tlit": "yatū",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْتُونَ",
        "answer": "they (could) bring",
        "pcklId": "125",
        "tlit": "yatūna",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَأْتِيَ",
        "answer": "you bring",
        "pcklId": "126",
        "tlit": "tatiya",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآتَيْنَا",
        "answer": "And We gave",
        "pcklId": "405",
        "tlit": "waātaynā",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآتِ",
        "answer": "And give",
        "pcklId": "406",
        "tlit": "waāti",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآتَيْنَا",
        "answer": "And We gave",
        "pcklId": "407",
        "tlit": "waātaynā",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآتَيْنَا",
        "answer": "And We gave",
        "pcklId": "408",
        "tlit": "waātaynā",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُوتِيَ",
        "answer": "is given",
        "pcklId": "409",
        "tlit": "ūtiya",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُوتِيتُمْ",
        "answer": "you have been given",
        "pcklId": "410",
        "tlit": "ūtītum",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "آتَيْنَا",
        "answer": "We had given",
        "pcklId": "411",
        "tlit": "ātaynā",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُوتُوا",
        "answer": "were given",
        "pcklId": "412",
        "tlit": "ūtū",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجْرًا",
        "answer": "(is) a reward",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "ajran",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجَلًا",
        "answer": "a term",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "ajalan",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحَدُهُمَا",
        "answer": "one of them",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "aḥaduhumā",
        "frequency": "85",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَتَّخِذُوا",
        "answer": "you take",
        "pcklId": "190",
        "tlit": "tattakhidhū",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاتَّخَذَ",
        "answer": "and He has taken",
        "pcklId": "191",
        "tlit": "wa-ittakhadha",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَاتَّخَذُوكَ",
        "answer": "surely they would take you",
        "pcklId": "192",
        "tlit": "la-ittakhadhūka",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَّخِذْ",
        "answer": "has not taken",
        "pcklId": "193",
        "tlit": "yattakhidh",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخَّرْتَنِ",
        "answer": "You give me respite",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "akhartani",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرَةِ",
        "answer": "the last",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "l-ākhirati",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْآخِرَةِ",
        "answer": "in the Hereafter",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "bil-ākhirati",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرَةَ",
        "answer": "the Hereafter",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "l-ākhirata",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَلْآخِرَةُ",
        "answer": "And surely the Hereafter",
        "pcklId": "90",
        "tlit": "walalākhiratu",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْآخِرَةِ",
        "answer": "in the Hereafter",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "bil-ākhirati",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرَةِ",
        "answer": "the Hereafter",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "l-ākhirati",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Hereafter",
        "pcklId": "93",
        "tlit": "l-ākhirati",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُخْرَىٰ",
        "answer": "(of) another",
        "pcklId": "199",
        "tlit": "ukh'rā",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُخْرَىٰ",
        "answer": "another time",
        "pcklId": "200",
        "tlit": "ukh'rā",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "آخَرَ",
        "answer": "another",
        "pcklId": "231",
        "tlit": "ākhara",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "آخَرَ",
        "answer": "other",
        "pcklId": "232",
        "tlit": "ākhara",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِخْوَانَ",
        "answer": "brothers",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "ikh'wāna",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "122",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذْ",
        "answer": "and when",
        "pcklId": "123",
        "tlit": "wa-idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "124",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذْ",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "125",
        "tlit": "wa-idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذْ",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "126",
        "tlit": "wa-idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "127",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "128",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَإِذَا",
        "answer": "So when",
        "pcklId": "138",
        "tlit": "fa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَإِذَا",
        "answer": "So when",
        "pcklId": "139",
        "tlit": "fa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "140",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "141",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "142",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "143",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَإِذَا",
        "answer": "Is it when",
        "pcklId": "144",
        "tlit": "a-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "145",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "146",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "147",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَإِذَا",
        "answer": "When",
        "pcklId": "148",
        "tlit": "a-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَإِذَا",
        "answer": "then when",
        "pcklId": "149",
        "tlit": "fa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "150",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذًا",
        "answer": "then",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "idhan",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذًا",
        "answer": "And then",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "wa-idhan",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذًا",
        "answer": "Then",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "idhan",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذًا",
        "answer": "But then",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "wa-idhan",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذًا",
        "answer": "then",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "idhan",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "آذَانِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their ears",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "ādhānihim",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "183",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "184",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضَ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "185",
        "tlit": "l-arḍa",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضُ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "186",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍu",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "187",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the land",
        "pcklId": "188",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "189",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "190",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضَ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "191",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍa",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "192",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the land",
        "pcklId": "193",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضَ",
        "answer": "(in) the land",
        "pcklId": "194",
        "tlit": "l-arḍa",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِسْرَائِيلَ",
        "answer": "(of) Israel",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "is'rāīla",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِسْرَائِيلَ",
        "answer": "(of) Israel",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "is'rāīla",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِسْرَائِيلَ",
        "answer": "(the) Children of Israel",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "is'rāīla",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِسْرَائِيلَ",
        "answer": "to the Children of Israel",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "is'rāīla",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُفٍّ",
        "answer": "a word of disrespect",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "uffin",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "226",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "227",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "228",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "229",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "230",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "but",
        "pcklId": "231",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "232",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "but",
        "pcklId": "233",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "234",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "235",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "236",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "237",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "238",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "239",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "240",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "241",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "242",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "243",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "244",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "Except",
        "pcklId": "245",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "246",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "but",
        "pcklId": "247",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "248",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "249",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "250",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "251",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(is) the One Who",
        "pcklId": "698",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "which",
        "pcklId": "699",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّتِي",
        "answer": "to that",
        "pcklId": "700",
        "tlit": "lillatī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "701",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "702",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّتِي",
        "answer": "which",
        "pcklId": "703",
        "tlit": "allatī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالَّتِي",
        "answer": "with what",
        "pcklId": "704",
        "tlit": "bi-allatī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "705",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "He Who",
        "pcklId": "706",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّتِي",
        "answer": "that",
        "pcklId": "707",
        "tlit": "allatī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those whom",
        "pcklId": "708",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "whom",
        "pcklId": "709",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّتِي",
        "answer": "which",
        "pcklId": "710",
        "tlit": "allatī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "whom",
        "pcklId": "711",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(is) the One Who",
        "pcklId": "712",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "that which",
        "pcklId": "713",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالَّذِي",
        "answer": "that which",
        "pcklId": "714",
        "tlit": "bi-alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "the One Who",
        "pcklId": "715",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "716",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "the One Who",
        "pcklId": "717",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلِيمًا",
        "answer": "painful",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "alīman",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَٰهًا",
        "answer": "god",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "ilāhan",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَٰهًا",
        "answer": "god",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "ilāhan",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "آلِهَةٌ",
        "answer": "gods",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "ālihatun",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1721",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah has forbidden",
        "pcklId": "1722",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1723",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1724",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Has Allah sent",
        "pcklId": "1725",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1726",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah guides",
        "pcklId": "1727",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1728",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1729",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "(is) for Allah",
        "pcklId": "1730",
        "tlit": "lillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "350",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "for",
        "pcklId": "351",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "352",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكَ",
        "answer": "to you",
        "pcklId": "353",
        "tlit": "ilayka",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "354",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكَ",
        "answer": "to you",
        "pcklId": "355",
        "tlit": "ilayka",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكَ",
        "answer": "at you",
        "pcklId": "356",
        "tlit": "ilayka",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "357",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "till",
        "pcklId": "358",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "359",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكَ",
        "answer": "to you",
        "pcklId": "360",
        "tlit": "ilayka",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِمْ",
        "answer": "to them",
        "pcklId": "361",
        "tlit": "ilayhim",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "till",
        "pcklId": "362",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكَ",
        "answer": "to you",
        "pcklId": "363",
        "tlit": "ilayka",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْ",
        "answer": "Or",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "am",
        "frequency": "137",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمَرْنَا",
        "answer": "We order",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "amarnā",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْرِ",
        "answer": "(the) affair",
        "pcklId": "153",
        "tlit": "amri",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِإِمَامِهِمْ",
        "answer": "with their record",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "bi-imāmihim",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِمَّا",
        "answer": "Whether",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "immā",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِمَّا",
        "answer": "And if",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "wa-immā",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَفَأَمِنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "Do you then feel secure",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "afa-amintum",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمِنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "do you feel secure",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "amintum",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "321",
        "tlit": "yu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "322",
        "tlit": "yu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُؤْمِنَ",
        "answer": "we will believe",
        "pcklId": "323",
        "tlit": "nu'mina",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُؤْمِنَ",
        "answer": "we will believe",
        "pcklId": "324",
        "tlit": "nu'mina",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُوا",
        "answer": "they believe",
        "pcklId": "325",
        "tlit": "yu'minū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمِنُوا",
        "answer": "Believe",
        "pcklId": "326",
        "tlit": "āminū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُؤْمِنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "327",
        "tlit": "tu'minū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُؤْمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "to the believers ",
        "pcklId": "749",
        "tlit": "l-mu'minīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُؤْمِنٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a believer",
        "pcklId": "750",
        "tlit": "mu'minun",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْمُؤْمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "for the believers",
        "pcklId": "751",
        "tlit": "lil'mu'minīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِنَاثًا",
        "answer": "daughters",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "ināthan",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْإِنْسُ",
        "answer": "the mankind",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "l-insu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْإِنْسَانُ",
        "answer": "the man",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "l-insānu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْإِنْسَانُ",
        "answer": "the man",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "l-insānu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِنْسَانٍ",
        "answer": "man",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "insānin",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْإِنْسَانِ",
        "answer": "to the man",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "lil'insāni",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْإِنْسَانُ",
        "answer": "man",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "l-insānu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُنَاسٍ",
        "answer": "human beings",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "unāsin",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْإِنْسَانِ",
        "answer": "man",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "l-insāni",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْإِنْسَانُ",
        "answer": "man",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "l-insānu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْأَوَّابِينَ",
        "answer": "to those who often turn (to Him)",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "lil'awwābīna",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُولَاهُمَا",
        "answer": "(for) the first of the two",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "ūlāhumā",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوَّلَ",
        "answer": "first",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "awwala",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوَّلَ",
        "answer": "(the) first",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "awwala",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَوَّلُونَ",
        "answer": "the former (people)",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "l-awalūna",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُولِي",
        "answer": "those of great military might",
        "pcklId": "101",
        "tlit": "ulī",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَأْوِيلًا",
        "answer": "(in) result",
        "pcklId": "167",
        "tlit": "tawīlan",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَأْوَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "Their abode",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "mawāhum",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَاتِنَا",
        "answer": "Our Signs",
        "pcklId": "175",
        "tlit": "āyātinā",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَتَيْنِ",
        "answer": "(as) two signs",
        "pcklId": "176",
        "tlit": "āyatayni",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَةَ",
        "answer": "(the) sign",
        "pcklId": "177",
        "tlit": "āyata",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَةَ",
        "answer": "(the) sign",
        "pcklId": "178",
        "tlit": "āyata",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْآيَاتِ",
        "answer": "the Signs",
        "pcklId": "179",
        "tlit": "bil-āyāti",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْآيَاتِ",
        "answer": "the Signs",
        "pcklId": "180",
        "tlit": "bil-āyāti",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَاتِنَا",
        "answer": "in Our Verses",
        "pcklId": "181",
        "tlit": "biāyātinā",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَاتٍ",
        "answer": "Signs",
        "pcklId": "182",
        "tlit": "āyātin",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَأْسٍ",
        "answer": "those of great military might",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "basin",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَحْرِ",
        "answer": "the sea",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "l-baḥri",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَحْرِ",
        "answer": "the sea",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "l-baḥri",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْبَحْرِ",
        "answer": "and the sea",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "wal-baḥri",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُبَذِّرْ",
        "answer": "spend",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "tubadhir",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَبْذِيرًا",
        "answer": "wastefully",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "tabdhīran",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُبَذِّرِينَ",
        "answer": "the spendthrifts",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-mubadhirīna",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَرِّ",
        "answer": "the land",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "l-bari",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَرِّ",
        "answer": "(of) the land",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "l-bari",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَرِّ",
        "answer": "the land",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "l-bari",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَارَكْنَا",
        "answer": "We blessed",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "bāraknā",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَبْسُطْهَا",
        "answer": "extend it",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "tabsuṭ'hā",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَبْسُطُ",
        "answer": "extends",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "yabsuṭu",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَسْطِ",
        "answer": "reach",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "l-basṭi",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُبَشِّرُ",
        "answer": "and gives glad tidings",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "wayubashiru",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَشَرًا",
        "answer": "a human",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "basharan",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَشَرًا",
        "answer": "a human",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "basharan",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُبَشِّرًا",
        "answer": "(as) a bearer of glad tidings",
        "pcklId": "116",
        "tlit": "mubashiran",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْبَصَرَ",
        "answer": "and the sight",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "wal-baṣara",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَصِيرُ",
        "answer": "the All-Seer",
        "pcklId": "114",
        "tlit": "l-baṣīru",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَصِيرًا",
        "answer": "All-Seer",
        "pcklId": "115",
        "tlit": "baṣīran",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَصِيرًا",
        "answer": "All-Seer",
        "pcklId": "116",
        "tlit": "baṣīran",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَصِيرًا",
        "answer": "All-Seer",
        "pcklId": "117",
        "tlit": "baṣīran",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَصَائِرَ",
        "answer": "(as) evidence",
        "pcklId": "135",
        "tlit": "baṣāira",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُبْصِرَةً",
        "answer": "visible",
        "pcklId": "144",
        "tlit": "mub'ṣiratan",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُبْصِرَةً",
        "answer": "(as) a visible sign",
        "pcklId": "145",
        "tlit": "mub'ṣiratan",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَاطِلُ",
        "answer": "the falsehood",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "l-bāṭilu",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَاطِلَ",
        "answer": "the falsehood",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "l-bāṭila",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعَثْنَا",
        "answer": "We raised",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "baʿathnā",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَبْعَثَ",
        "answer": "We have sent",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "nabʿatha",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَبْعَثَكَ",
        "answer": "will raise you",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "yabʿathaka",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَبَعَثَ",
        "answer": "Has Allah sent",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "abaʿatha",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَمَبْعُوثُونَ",
        "answer": "surely (be) resurrected",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "lamabʿūthūna",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَمَبْعُوثُونَ",
        "answer": "surely (be) resurrected",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "lamabʿūthūna",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "baʿdi",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِهِ",
        "answer": "after him",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "baʿdihi",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْضَهُمْ",
        "answer": "some of them",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "baʿḍahum",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْضٍ",
        "answer": "others",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "baʿḍin",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْضَ",
        "answer": "some",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "baʿḍa",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْضٍ",
        "answer": "others",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "baʿḍin",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْضُهُمْ",
        "answer": "some of them",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "baʿḍuhum",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِبَعْضٍ",
        "answer": "to some others",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "libaʿḍin",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِتَبْتَغُوا",
        "answer": "that you may seek",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "litabtaghū",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَابْتَغَوْا",
        "answer": "surely they (would) have sought",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "la-ib'taghaw",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَبْتَغُونَ",
        "answer": "seek",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "yabtaghūna",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِتَبْتَغُوا",
        "answer": "that you may seek",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "litabtaghū",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَابْتَغِ",
        "answer": "but seek",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "wa-ib'taghi",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "ابْتِغَاءَ",
        "answer": "seeking",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "ib'tighāa",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبُكْمًا",
        "answer": "and dumb",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "wabuk'man",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَبْكُونَ",
        "answer": "weeping",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yabkūna",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَبْلُغَنَّ",
        "answer": "reach",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "yablughanna",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَبْلُغَ",
        "answer": "he reaches",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "yablugha",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَبْلُغَ",
        "answer": "reach",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "tablugha",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَابْنَ",
        "answer": "and the wayfarer",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "wa-ib'na",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِبَنِي",
        "answer": "for the Children",
        "pcklId": "133",
        "tlit": "libanī",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَنِي",
        "answer": "(the) Children",
        "pcklId": "134",
        "tlit": "banī",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبَنِينَ",
        "answer": "and sons",
        "pcklId": "135",
        "tlit": "wabanīna",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْبَنِينَ",
        "answer": "sons",
        "pcklId": "136",
        "tlit": "bil-banīna",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَنِي",
        "answer": "(the) children of Adam",
        "pcklId": "137",
        "tlit": "banī",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَنِي",
        "answer": "(the) Children of Israel",
        "pcklId": "138",
        "tlit": "banī",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِبَنِي",
        "answer": "to the Children of Israel",
        "pcklId": "139",
        "tlit": "libanī",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْتٌ",
        "answer": "a house",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "baytun",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَكَ",
        "answer": "between you",
        "pcklId": "161",
        "tlit": "baynaka",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبَيْنَ",
        "answer": "and between",
        "pcklId": "162",
        "tlit": "wabayna",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَهُمْ",
        "answer": "between them",
        "pcklId": "163",
        "tlit": "baynahum",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنِي",
        "answer": "between me",
        "pcklId": "164",
        "tlit": "baynī",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبَيْنَكُمْ",
        "answer": "and between you",
        "pcklId": "165",
        "tlit": "wabaynakum",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَ",
        "answer": "between",
        "pcklId": "166",
        "tlit": "bayna",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيِّنَاتٍ",
        "answer": "clear",
        "pcklId": "383",
        "tlit": "bayyinātin",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُبِينًا",
        "answer": "clear",
        "pcklId": "419",
        "tlit": "mubīnan",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِيُتَبِّرُوا",
        "answer": "and to destroy",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "waliyutabbirū",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَتْبِيرًا",
        "answer": "(with) destruction",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "tatbīran",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَبِعَكَ",
        "answer": "follows you",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "tabiʿaka",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَتَّبِعُونَ",
        "answer": "you follow",
        "pcklId": "97",
        "tlit": "tattabiʿūna",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَبِيعًا",
        "answer": "an avenger",
        "pcklId": "162",
        "tlit": "tabīʿan",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُتْرَفِيهَا",
        "answer": "its wealthy people",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "mut'rafīhā",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "تِسْعَ",
        "answer": "nine",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "tis'ʿa",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُتْلَىٰ",
        "answer": "it is recited",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "yut'lā",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَارَةً",
        "answer": "another time",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "tāratan",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "ثَبَّتْنَاكَ",
        "answer": "We (had) strengthened you",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "thabbatnāka",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَثْبُورًا",
        "answer": "(you are) destroyed",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "mathbūran",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجِبَالَ",
        "answer": "the mountains",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "l-jibāla",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَدِيدًا",
        "answer": "new",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "jadīdan",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَدِيدًا",
        "answer": "new",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "jadīdan",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَزَاؤُكُمْ",
        "answer": "(is) your recompense ",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "jazāukum",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَزَاءً",
        "answer": "a recompense",
        "pcklId": "93",
        "tlit": "jazāan",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَزَاؤُهُمْ",
        "answer": "(is) their recompense",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "jazāuhum",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَعَلْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "and made it",
        "pcklId": "116",
        "tlit": "wajaʿalnāhu",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَعَلْنَاكُمْ",
        "answer": "and made you",
        "pcklId": "117",
        "tlit": "wajaʿalnākum",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَعَلْنَا",
        "answer": "And We have made",
        "pcklId": "118",
        "tlit": "wajaʿalnā",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَعَلْنَا",
        "answer": "And We have made",
        "pcklId": "119",
        "tlit": "wajaʿalnā",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَعَلْنَا",
        "answer": "and We made",
        "pcklId": "120",
        "tlit": "wajaʿalnā",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَعَلْنَا",
        "answer": "We have made",
        "pcklId": "121",
        "tlit": "jaʿalnā",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَجْعَلْ",
        "answer": "make",
        "pcklId": "122",
        "tlit": "tajʿal",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَجْعَلْ",
        "answer": "make",
        "pcklId": "123",
        "tlit": "tajʿal",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَعَلْنَا",
        "answer": "We have made",
        "pcklId": "124",
        "tlit": "jaʿalnā",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَجْعَلْ",
        "answer": "make",
        "pcklId": "125",
        "tlit": "tajʿal",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَعَلْنَا",
        "answer": "We place",
        "pcklId": "126",
        "tlit": "jaʿalnā",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَعَلْنَا",
        "answer": "And We have placed",
        "pcklId": "127",
        "tlit": "wajaʿalnā",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَعَلْنَا",
        "answer": "We made",
        "pcklId": "128",
        "tlit": "jaʿalnā",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاجْعَلْ",
        "answer": "and make",
        "pcklId": "129",
        "tlit": "wa-ij'ʿal",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَعَلَ",
        "answer": "And He has made",
        "pcklId": "130",
        "tlit": "wajaʿala",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَجْلِبْ",
        "answer": "and assault",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wa-ajlib",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "اجْتَمَعَتِ",
        "answer": "gathered",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "ij'tamaʿati",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَمِيعًا",
        "answer": "all",
        "pcklId": "101",
        "tlit": "jamīʿan",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَانِبَ",
        "answer": "side",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "jāniba",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِجَانِبِهِ",
        "answer": "on his side",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "bijānibihi",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَنَاحَ",
        "answer": "(the) wing",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "janāḥa",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْجِنُّ",
        "answer": "and the jinn",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "wal-jinu",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَنَّةٌ",
        "answer": "a garden",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "jannatun",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَجْهَرْ",
        "answer": "be loud",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "tajhar",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَسْتَجِيبُونَ",
        "answer": "and you will respond",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "fatastajībūna",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَجَاسُوا",
        "answer": "and they entered",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "fajāsū",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَ",
        "answer": "came",
        "pcklId": "136",
        "tlit": "jāa",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَ",
        "answer": "came",
        "pcklId": "137",
        "tlit": "jāa",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَ",
        "answer": "Has come",
        "pcklId": "138",
        "tlit": "jāa",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَهُمُ",
        "answer": "came to them",
        "pcklId": "139",
        "tlit": "jāahumu",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَهُمْ",
        "answer": "he came to them",
        "pcklId": "140",
        "tlit": "jāahum",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَ",
        "answer": "comes",
        "pcklId": "141",
        "tlit": "jāa",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "جِئْنَا",
        "answer": "We will bring",
        "pcklId": "142",
        "tlit": "ji'nā",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "حِجَابًا",
        "answer": "a barrier",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ḥijāban",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "حِجَارَةً",
        "answer": "stones",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "ḥijāratan",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَدِيدًا",
        "answer": "iron",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "ḥadīdan",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَحْذُورًا",
        "answer": "(ever) feared",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "maḥdhūran",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَرَّمَ",
        "answer": "Allah has forbidden",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "ḥarrama",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَرَامِ",
        "answer": "Al-Masjid Al-Haraam",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "l-ḥarāmi",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَسِيبًا",
        "answer": "(as) accountant",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "ḥasīban",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْحِسَابَ",
        "answer": "and the account",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "wal-ḥisāba",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَحْسُورًا",
        "answer": "insolvent",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "maḥsūran",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحْسَنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you do good",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "aḥsantum",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحْسَنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you do good",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "aḥsantum",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحْسَنُ",
        "answer": "best",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "aḥsanu",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَحْسَنُ",
        "answer": "and best",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "wa-aḥsanu",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحْسَنُ",
        "answer": "(is) best",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "aḥsanu",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحُسْنَىٰ",
        "answer": "the Most Beautiful Names",
        "pcklId": "110",
        "tlit": "l-ḥus'nā",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِحْسَانًا",
        "answer": "(be) good",
        "pcklId": "151",
        "tlit": "iḥ'sānan",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَحْشُرُهُمْ",
        "answer": "And We will gather them",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "wanaḥshuruhum",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَاصِبًا",
        "answer": "a storm of stones",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ḥāṣiban",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَصِيرًا",
        "answer": "a prison-bed",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "ḥaṣīran",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَحْظُورًا",
        "answer": "restricted",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "maḥẓūran",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَحَقَّ",
        "answer": "so (is) proved true",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "faḥaqqa",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَقَّهُ",
        "answer": "his right",
        "pcklId": "154",
        "tlit": "ḥaqqahu",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "by right",
        "pcklId": "155",
        "tlit": "bil-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَقُّ",
        "answer": "the truth",
        "pcklId": "156",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaqu",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبِالْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "And with the truth",
        "pcklId": "157",
        "tlit": "wabil-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبِالْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "and with the truth",
        "pcklId": "158",
        "tlit": "wabil-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحِكْمَةِ",
        "answer": "the wisdom",
        "pcklId": "98",
        "tlit": "l-ḥik'mati",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَلِيمًا",
        "answer": "Ever-Forbearing",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "ḥalīman",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِحَمْدِهِ",
        "answer": "His Praise",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "biḥamdihi",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِحَمْدِهِ",
        "answer": "with His Praise",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "biḥamdihi",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَمْدُ",
        "answer": "All Praise",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "l-ḥamdu",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَحْمُودًا",
        "answer": "praiseworthy",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "maḥmūdan",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَمَلْنَا",
        "answer": "We carried",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "ḥamalnā",
        "frequency": "64",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَحَمَلْنَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "and We carried them",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "waḥamalnāhum",
        "frequency": "64",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَأَحْتَنِكَنَّ",
        "answer": "I will surely destroy",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "la-aḥtanikanna",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحَاطَ",
        "answer": "has encompassed",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "aḥāṭa",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَوْلَهُ",
        "answer": "its surroundings",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "ḥawlahu",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحْوِيلًا",
        "answer": "(to) transfer (it)",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "taḥwīlan",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحْوِيلًا",
        "answer": "any alteration",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "taḥwīlan",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَيَاةِ",
        "answer": "(in) the life",
        "pcklId": "132",
        "tlit": "l-ḥayati",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَبِيرًا",
        "answer": "All-Aware",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "khabīran",
        "frequency": "52",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَبِيرًا",
        "answer": "All-Aware",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "khabīran",
        "frequency": "52",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَبِيرًا",
        "answer": "All-Aware",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "khabīran",
        "frequency": "52",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَبَتْ",
        "answer": "it subsides",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "khabat",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَخْذُولًا",
        "answer": "forsaken",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "makhdhūlan",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنُخْرِجُ",
        "answer": "and We will bring forth",
        "pcklId": "97",
        "tlit": "wanukh'riju",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيُخْرِجُوكَ",
        "answer": "that they evict you",
        "pcklId": "98",
        "tlit": "liyukh'rijūka",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَخْرِجْنِي",
        "answer": "and cause me to exit",
        "pcklId": "99",
        "tlit": "wa-akhrij'nī",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُخْرَجَ",
        "answer": "an exit",
        "pcklId": "178",
        "tlit": "mukh'raja",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخِرُّونَ",
        "answer": "they fall",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yakhirrūna",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَخِرُّونَ",
        "answer": "And they fall",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "wayakhirrūna",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَخْرِقَ",
        "answer": "tear",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "takhriqa",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَزَائِنَ",
        "answer": "the treasures",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "khazāina",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَسَارًا",
        "answer": "(in) loss",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "khasāran",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخْسِفَ",
        "answer": "He will cause to swallow",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yakhsifa",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "خُشُوعًا",
        "answer": "(in) humility",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "khushūʿan",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَشْيَةَ",
        "answer": "(for) fear",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "khashyata",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَشْيَةَ",
        "answer": "(out of) fear",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "khashyata",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "خِطْئًا",
        "answer": "a sin",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "khiṭ'an",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُخَافِتْ",
        "answer": "be silent",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "tukhāfit",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاخْفِضْ",
        "answer": "And lower",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wa-ikh'fiḍ",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "خِلَافَكَ",
        "answer": "after you",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "khilāfaka",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَقْتَ",
        "answer": "You created",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "khalaqta",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَقْنَا",
        "answer": "We have created",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "khalaqnā",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَقَ",
        "answer": "created",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "khalaqa",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخْلُقَ",
        "answer": "create",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "yakhluqa",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلْقًا",
        "answer": "(as) a creation",
        "pcklId": "207",
        "tlit": "khalqan",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلْقًا",
        "answer": "a creation",
        "pcklId": "208",
        "tlit": "khalqan",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلْقًا",
        "answer": "(as) a creation",
        "pcklId": "209",
        "tlit": "khalqan",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "خِلَالَ",
        "answer": "the inner most part",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "khilāla",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "خِلَالَهَا",
        "answer": "within them",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "khilālahā",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلِيلًا",
        "answer": "(as) a friend",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "khalīlan",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَخَافُونَ",
        "answer": "and fear",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "wayakhāfūna",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنُخَوِّفُهُمْ",
        "answer": "And We threaten them",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "wanukhawwifuhum",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَخْوِيفًا",
        "answer": "(as) a warning",
        "pcklId": "122",
        "tlit": "takhwīfan",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْخَيْرِ",
        "answer": "for the good",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "bil-khayri",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) good",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "khayrun",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِخَيْلِكَ",
        "answer": "with your cavalry",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "bikhaylika",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَدْبَارِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their backs",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "adbārihim",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَدْحُورًا",
        "answer": "rejected",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "madḥūran",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَدْحُورًا",
        "answer": "abandoned",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "madḥūran",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِيَدْخُلُوا",
        "answer": "and to enter",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "waliyadkhulū",
        "frequency": "126",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَخَلُوهُ",
        "answer": "they (had) entered it",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "dakhalūhu",
        "frequency": "126",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَدْخِلْنِي",
        "answer": "Cause me to enter",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "adkhil'nī",
        "frequency": "126",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُدْخَلَ",
        "answer": "an entrance",
        "pcklId": "123",
        "tlit": "mud'khala",
        "frequency": "126",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَرَجَاتٍ",
        "answer": "(in) degrees",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "darajātin",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَدْعُ",
        "answer": "And prays",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "wayadʿu",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَدْعُوكُمْ",
        "answer": "He will call you",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "yadʿūkum",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "ادْعُوا",
        "answer": "Call",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "id'ʿū",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَدْعُونَ",
        "answer": "they call",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "yadʿūna",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَدْعُونَ",
        "answer": "you call",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "tadʿūna",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَدْعُو",
        "answer": "We will call",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "nadʿū",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "ادْعُوا",
        "answer": "Invoke",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "id'ʿū",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "ادْعُوا",
        "answer": "invoke",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "id'ʿū",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَدْعُوا",
        "answer": "you invoke",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "tadʿū",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُعَاءَهُ",
        "answer": "(as) he prays",
        "pcklId": "178",
        "tlit": "duʿāahu",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِدُلُوكِ",
        "answer": "at the decline",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "lidulūki",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَدَمَّرْنَاهَا",
        "answer": "and We destroy it",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "fadammarnāhā",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَدْمِيرًا",
        "answer": "(with) destruction",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "tadmīran",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدِّيَارِ",
        "answer": "(of) the homes",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "l-diyāri",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِي",
        "answer": "other than Me",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "dūnī",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِهِ",
        "answer": "besides Him",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "dūnihi",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِهِ",
        "answer": "besides Him",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "dūnihi",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذُرِّيَّةَ",
        "answer": "Offsprings",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "dhurriyyata",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذُرِّيَّتَهُ",
        "answer": "his offspring",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "dhurriyyatahu",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْأَذْقَانِ",
        "answer": "on their faces",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "lil'adhqāni",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْأَذْقَانِ",
        "answer": "on their faces",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "lil'adhqāni",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذَكَرْتَ",
        "answer": "you mention",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "dhakarta",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيَذَّكَّرُوا",
        "answer": "that they may take heed",
        "pcklId": "124",
        "tlit": "liyadhakkarū",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "الذُّلِّ",
        "answer": "(of) humility",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "l-dhuli",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "الذُّلِّ",
        "answer": "weakness",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "l-dhuli",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَذْمُومًا",
        "answer": "disgraced",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "madhmūman",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَذْمُومًا",
        "answer": "disgraced",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "madhmūman",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِذُنُوبِ",
        "answer": "concerning the sins",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "bidhunūbi",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "اذْهَبْ",
        "answer": "Go",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "idh'hab",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَنَذْهَبَنَّ",
        "answer": "We (would) have surely taken away",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "lanadhhabanna",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَأَذَقْنَاكَ",
        "answer": "We (would) have made you taste",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "la-adhaqnāka",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "رُءُوسَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their heads",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "ruūsahum",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرَأَيْتَكَ",
        "answer": "Do You see",
        "pcklId": "98",
        "tlit": "ara-aytaka",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرَوْا",
        "answer": "they see",
        "pcklId": "99",
        "tlit": "yaraw",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِنُرِيَهُ",
        "answer": "that We may show him",
        "pcklId": "288",
        "tlit": "linuriyahu",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرَيْنَاكَ",
        "answer": "We showed you",
        "pcklId": "289",
        "tlit": "araynāka",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرُّؤْيَا",
        "answer": "the vision",
        "pcklId": "322",
        "tlit": "l-ru'yā",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّكُمْ",
        "answer": "that your Lord",
        "pcklId": "386",
        "tlit": "rabbukum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكُمْ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "387",
        "tlit": "rabbikum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِرَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "(is) your Lord",
        "pcklId": "388",
        "tlit": "birabbika",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "(of) your Lord",
        "pcklId": "389",
        "tlit": "rabbika",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "(of) your Lord",
        "pcklId": "390",
        "tlit": "rabbika",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "391",
        "tlit": "rabbuka",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّ",
        "answer": "My Lord",
        "pcklId": "392",
        "tlit": "rabbi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّكُمْ",
        "answer": "Your Lord",
        "pcklId": "393",
        "tlit": "rabbukum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِرَبِّهِ",
        "answer": "to his Lord",
        "pcklId": "394",
        "tlit": "lirabbihi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "395",
        "tlit": "rabbika",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "396",
        "tlit": "rabbaka",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "397",
        "tlit": "rabbika",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّكَ",
        "answer": "(from) your Lord",
        "pcklId": "398",
        "tlit": "rabbuka",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّكُمْ",
        "answer": "Then has your Lord chosen (for) you",
        "pcklId": "399",
        "tlit": "rabbukum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "400",
        "tlit": "rabbaka",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّكُمْ",
        "answer": "Your Lord",
        "pcklId": "401",
        "tlit": "rabbukum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَبُّكَ",
        "answer": "And your Lord",
        "pcklId": "402",
        "tlit": "warabbuka",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِمُ",
        "answer": "their Lord",
        "pcklId": "403",
        "tlit": "rabbihimu",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "(of) your Lord",
        "pcklId": "404",
        "tlit": "rabbika",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "405",
        "tlit": "rabbaka",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِرَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "(is) your Lord",
        "pcklId": "406",
        "tlit": "birabbika",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّكُمُ",
        "answer": "Your Lord",
        "pcklId": "407",
        "tlit": "rabbukumu",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "408",
        "tlit": "rabbuka",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّ",
        "answer": "My Lord",
        "pcklId": "409",
        "tlit": "rabbi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَرَبُّكُمْ",
        "answer": "but your Lord",
        "pcklId": "410",
        "tlit": "farabbukum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّي",
        "answer": "(of) my Lord",
        "pcklId": "411",
        "tlit": "rabbī",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "412",
        "tlit": "rabbika",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّي",
        "answer": "my Lord",
        "pcklId": "413",
        "tlit": "rabbī",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّي",
        "answer": "(of) my Lord",
        "pcklId": "414",
        "tlit": "rabbī",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّ",
        "answer": "(the) Lord",
        "pcklId": "415",
        "tlit": "rabbu",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّنَا",
        "answer": "our Lord",
        "pcklId": "416",
        "tlit": "rabbinā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّنَا",
        "answer": "(of) our Lord",
        "pcklId": "417",
        "tlit": "rabbinā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّيَانِي",
        "answer": "they brought me up",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "rabbayānī",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَجُلًا",
        "answer": "a man",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "rajulan",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَجِلِكَ",
        "answer": "and infantry",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "warajilika",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرْجُوهَا",
        "answer": "which you expect",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "tarjūhā",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَرْجُونَ",
        "answer": "and they hope",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "wayarjūna",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرْحَمَكُمْ",
        "answer": "(may) have mercy upon you",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "yarḥamakum",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "ارْحَمْهُمَا",
        "answer": "Have mercy on both of them",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "ir'ḥamhumā",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرْحَمْكُمْ",
        "answer": "He will have mercy on you",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "yarḥamkum",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّحْمَٰنَ",
        "answer": "the Most Gracious",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "l-raḥmāna",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّحْمَةِ",
        "answer": "[the] mercy",
        "pcklId": "151",
        "tlit": "l-raḥmati",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحْمَةٍ",
        "answer": "mercy",
        "pcklId": "152",
        "tlit": "raḥmatin",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحْمَتَهُ",
        "answer": "(for) His mercy",
        "pcklId": "153",
        "tlit": "raḥmatahu",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَحْمَةٌ",
        "answer": "and a mercy",
        "pcklId": "154",
        "tlit": "waraḥmatun",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحْمَةً",
        "answer": "a mercy",
        "pcklId": "155",
        "tlit": "raḥmatan",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحْمَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Mercy",
        "pcklId": "156",
        "tlit": "raḥmati",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحِيمًا",
        "answer": "Ever Merciful",
        "pcklId": "329",
        "tlit": "raḥīman",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَدَدْنَا",
        "answer": "We gave back",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "radadnā",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَرْزُقُهُمْ",
        "answer": "(We) provide for them",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "narzuquhum",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَزَقْنَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "and We have provided them",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "warazaqnāhum",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرِّزْقَ",
        "answer": "the provision",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "l-riz'qa",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْسَلْنَاكَ",
        "answer": "We have sent you",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "arsalnāka",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُرْسِلَ",
        "answer": "We send",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "nur'sila",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُرْسِلُ",
        "answer": "We send",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "nur'silu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُرْسِلَ",
        "answer": "send",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "yur'sila",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيُرْسِلَ",
        "answer": "and send",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "fayur'sila",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْسَلْنَا",
        "answer": "We sent",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "arsalnā",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْسَلْنَاكَ",
        "answer": "We sent you",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "arsalnāka",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولًا",
        "answer": "a Messenger",
        "pcklId": "308",
        "tlit": "rasūlan",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "رُسُلِنَا",
        "answer": "Our Messengers",
        "pcklId": "309",
        "tlit": "rusulinā",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولًا",
        "answer": "a Messenger",
        "pcklId": "310",
        "tlit": "rasūlan",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولًا",
        "answer": "Messenger",
        "pcklId": "311",
        "tlit": "rasūlan",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولًا",
        "answer": "(as) a Messenger",
        "pcklId": "312",
        "tlit": "rasūlan",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرُفَاتًا",
        "answer": "and crumbled particles",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "warufātan",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرُفَاتًا",
        "answer": "and crumbled particles",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "warufātan",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرْقَىٰ",
        "answer": "you ascend",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "tarqā",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِرُقِيِّكَ",
        "answer": "in your ascension",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "liruqiyyika",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرْكَنُ",
        "answer": "(would) have inclined",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "tarkanu",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرُّوحِ",
        "answer": "the soul",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "l-rūḥi",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرُّوحُ",
        "answer": "The soul",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "l-rūḥu",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرِّيحِ",
        "answer": "the wind",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "l-rīḥi",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرَدْنَا",
        "answer": "We intend",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "aradnā",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُرِيدُ",
        "answer": "desire",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "yurīdu",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُرِيدُ",
        "answer": "We intend",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "nurīdu",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرَادَ",
        "answer": "desires",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "arāda",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَرَادَ",
        "answer": "So he intended",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "fa-arāda",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَيْبَ",
        "answer": "doubt",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "rayba",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "زَبُورًا",
        "answer": "Zaboor",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "zabūran",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُزْجِي",
        "answer": "drives",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yuz'jī",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "زُخْرُفٍ",
        "answer": "ornament",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "zukh'rufin",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "زَعَمْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you claimed",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "zaʿamtum",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "زَعَمْتَ",
        "answer": "you have claimed",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "zaʿamta",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "الزِّنَا",
        "answer": "adultery",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-zinā",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَزَهَقَ",
        "answer": "and perished",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wazahaqa",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "زَهُوقًا",
        "answer": "(bound) to perish",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "zahūqan",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَزِيدُهُمْ",
        "answer": "it increases them",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "yazīduhum",
        "frequency": "61",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَزِيدُهُمْ",
        "answer": "it increases them",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "yazīduhum",
        "frequency": "61",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَزِيدُ",
        "answer": "it increases",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "yazīdu",
        "frequency": "61",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "زِدْنَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "We (will) increase (for) them",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "zid'nāhum",
        "frequency": "61",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَزِيدُهُمْ",
        "answer": "and it increases them",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "wayazīduhum",
        "frequency": "61",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَسْأَلُونَكَ",
        "answer": "And they ask you",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "wayasalūnaka",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاسْأَلْ",
        "answer": "so ask",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "fasal",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَسْئُولًا",
        "answer": "questioned",
        "pcklId": "124",
        "tlit": "masūlan",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَسْئُولًا",
        "answer": "questioned",
        "pcklId": "125",
        "tlit": "masūlan",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُسَبِّحُ",
        "answer": "Glorify",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "tusabbiḥu",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُسَبِّحُ",
        "answer": "glorifies",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "yusabbiḥu",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُبْحَانَ",
        "answer": "Exalted",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "sub'ḥāna",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُبْحَانَهُ",
        "answer": "Glorified is He",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "sub'ḥānahu",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُبْحَانَ",
        "answer": "Glorified (is)",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "sub'ḥāna",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُبْحَانَ",
        "answer": "Glory be to",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "sub'ḥāna",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَسْبِيحَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their glorification",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "tasbīḥahum",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّبْعُ",
        "answer": "the seven heavens",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "l-sabʿu",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّبِيلِ",
        "answer": "and the wayfarer",
        "pcklId": "107",
        "tlit": "l-sabīli",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلًا",
        "answer": "way",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "tlit": "sabīlan",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلًا",
        "answer": "a way",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "tlit": "sabīlan",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلًا",
        "answer": "(find) a way",
        "pcklId": "110",
        "tlit": "sabīlan",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلًا",
        "answer": "(from the) path",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "tlit": "sabīlan",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلًا",
        "answer": "(in) way",
        "pcklId": "112",
        "tlit": "sabīlan",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلًا",
        "answer": "a way",
        "pcklId": "113",
        "tlit": "sabīlan",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَسْتُورًا",
        "answer": "hidden",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "mastūran",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْجُدُوا",
        "answer": "Prostrate",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "us'judū",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَسَجَدُوا",
        "answer": "So they prostrated",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "fasajadū",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَأَسْجُدُ",
        "answer": "Shall I prostrate",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "a-asjudu",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَسْجِدِ",
        "answer": "Al-Masjid Al-Haraam",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "l-masjidi",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَسْجِدِ",
        "answer": "Al-Masjid Al-Aqsa",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "l-masjidi",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَسْجِدَ",
        "answer": "the Masjid",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "l-masjida",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُجَّدًا",
        "answer": "(in) prostration",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "sujjadan",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَسْحُورًا",
        "answer": "bewitched",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "masḥūran",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَسْحُورًا",
        "answer": "(you are) bewitched",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "masḥūran",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُسْرِفْ",
        "answer": "he should exceed",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yus'rif",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَسْرَىٰ",
        "answer": "took",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "asrā",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَسْطُورًا",
        "answer": "written",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "masṭūran",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَعِيرًا",
        "answer": "the blazing fire",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "saʿīran",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَسَعَىٰ",
        "answer": "and exerts",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "wasaʿā",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَعْيَهَا",
        "answer": "the effort",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "saʿyahā",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَعْيُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their effort",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "saʿyuhum",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُسْقِطَ",
        "answer": "you cause to fall",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "tus'qiṭa",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْكُنُوا",
        "answer": "Dwell",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "us'kunū",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمِسْكِينَ",
        "answer": "and the needy",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "wal-mis'kīna",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُلْطَانًا",
        "answer": "an authority",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "sul'ṭānan",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُلْطَانٌ",
        "answer": "any authority",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "sul'ṭānun",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُلْطَانًا",
        "answer": "an authority",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "sul'ṭānan",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَمِعُونَ",
        "answer": "they listen",
        "pcklId": "95",
        "tlit": "yastamiʿūna",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَمِعُونَ",
        "answer": "they listen",
        "pcklId": "96",
        "tlit": "yastamiʿūna",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمْعَ",
        "answer": "the hearing",
        "pcklId": "120",
        "tlit": "l-samʿa",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمِيعُ",
        "answer": "(is) the All-Hearer",
        "pcklId": "160",
        "tlit": "l-samīʿu",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَسْمَاءُ",
        "answer": "the Most Beautiful Names",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "l-asmāu",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتُ",
        "answer": "the seven heavens",
        "pcklId": "153",
        "tlit": "l-samāwātu",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "the heavens",
        "pcklId": "154",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاءَ",
        "answer": "the sky",
        "pcklId": "155",
        "tlit": "l-samāa",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاءِ",
        "answer": "the sky",
        "pcklId": "156",
        "tlit": "l-samāi",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاءِ",
        "answer": "the heaven",
        "pcklId": "157",
        "tlit": "l-samāi",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "the heavens",
        "pcklId": "158",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "(of) the heavens",
        "pcklId": "159",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُنَّةَ",
        "answer": "(Such is Our) Way",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "sunnata",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِسُنَّتِنَا",
        "answer": "(in) Our way",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "lisunnatinā",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "السِّنِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the years",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "l-sinīna",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيَسُوءُوا",
        "answer": "to sadden",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "liyasūū",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَسَاءَ",
        "answer": "and (an) evil",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "wasāa",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَسَأْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you do evil",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "asatum",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَيِّئُهُ",
        "answer": "[its] evil",
        "pcklId": "107",
        "tlit": "sayyi-uhu",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالشَّجَرَةَ",
        "answer": "and the tree",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "wal-shajarata",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَشُدَّهُ",
        "answer": "his maturity",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "ashuddahu",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَدِيدٍ",
        "answer": "those of great military might",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "shadīdin",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَدِيدًا",
        "answer": "severe",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "shadīdan",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالشَّرِّ",
        "answer": "for evil",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "bil-shari",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّرُّ",
        "answer": "the evil",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "l-sharu",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَشَارِكْهُمْ",
        "answer": "and be a partner",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "washārik'hum",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَرِيكٌ",
        "answer": "a partner",
        "pcklId": "100",
        "tlit": "sharīkun",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّيَاطِينِ",
        "answer": "(of) the devils",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "l-shayāṭīni",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّيْطَانُ",
        "answer": "the Shaitaan",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "l-shayṭānu",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّيْطَانَ",
        "answer": "the Shaitaan",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "l-shayṭāna",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّيْطَانَ",
        "answer": "the Shaitaan",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "l-shayṭāna",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّيْطَانُ",
        "answer": "the Shaitaan",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "l-shayṭānu",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "شِفَاءٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a healing",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "shifāon",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَكُورًا",
        "answer": "grateful",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "shakūran",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَشْكُورًا",
        "answer": "(is) appreciated",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "mashkūran",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَاكِلَتِهِ",
        "answer": "his manner",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "shākilatihi",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّمْسِ",
        "answer": "(of) the sun",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "l-shamsi",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَهِيدًا",
        "answer": "(as) a witness",
        "pcklId": "125",
        "tlit": "shahīdan",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَشْهُودًا",
        "answer": "ever witnessed",
        "pcklId": "158",
        "tlit": "mashhūdan",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "We will",
        "pcklId": "115",
        "tlit": "nashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "116",
        "tlit": "yashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَأْ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "117",
        "tlit": "yasha",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَأْ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "118",
        "tlit": "yasha",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "شِئْنَا",
        "answer": "We willed",
        "pcklId": "119",
        "tlit": "shi'nā",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing ",
        "pcklId": "373",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "374",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْئًا",
        "answer": "(in) something",
        "pcklId": "375",
        "tlit": "shayan",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "صُدُورِكُمْ",
        "answer": "your breasts",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "ṣudūrikum",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "صِدْقٍ",
        "answer": "sound",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "ṣid'qin",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "صِدْقٍ",
        "answer": "sound",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "ṣid'qin",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَرَّفْنَا",
        "answer": "We have explained",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "ṣarrafnā",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَرَّفْنَا",
        "answer": "We have explained",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "ṣarrafnā",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَغِيرًا",
        "answer": "(when I was) small",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ṣaghīran",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَفَأَصْفَاكُمْ",
        "answer": "Then has your Lord chosen (for) you",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "afa-aṣfākum",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَالِحِينَ",
        "answer": "righteous",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "ṣāliḥīna",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّالِحَاتِ",
        "answer": "the righteous deeds",
        "pcklId": "125",
        "tlit": "l-ṣāliḥāti",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّلَاةَ",
        "answer": "the prayer",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "l-ṣalata",
        "frequency": "99",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِصَلَاتِكَ",
        "answer": "in your prayers",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "biṣalātika",
        "frequency": "99",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَصْلَاهَا",
        "answer": "he will burn",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yaṣlāhā",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَصُمًّا",
        "answer": "and deaf",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "waṣumman",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِصَوْتِكَ",
        "answer": "with your voice",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "biṣawtika",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضَرَبُوا",
        "answer": "they put forth",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "ḍarabū",
        "frequency": "58",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "الضُّرِّ",
        "answer": "the misfortunes",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "l-ḍuri",
        "frequency": "74",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "الضُّرُّ",
        "answer": "the hardship",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "l-ḍuru",
        "frequency": "74",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضِعْفَ",
        "answer": "double",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "ḍiʿ'fa",
        "frequency": "52",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَضِعْفَ",
        "answer": "and double",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "waḍiʿ'fa",
        "frequency": "52",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضَلَّ",
        "answer": "goes astray",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "ḍalla",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَضِلُّ",
        "answer": "he goes astray",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "yaḍillu",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَضَلُّوا",
        "answer": "but they have gone astray",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "faḍallū",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضَلَّ",
        "answer": "lost",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "ḍalla",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُضْلِلْ",
        "answer": "He lets go astray ",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "yuḍ'lil",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَضَلُّ",
        "answer": "and more astray",
        "pcklId": "119",
        "tlit": "wa-aḍallu",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "طُغْيَانًا",
        "answer": "(in) transgression",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "ṭugh'yānan",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُطْمَئِنِّينَ",
        "answer": "securely",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "muṭ'ma-innīna",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَطِيعُونَ",
        "answer": "they can",
        "pcklId": "95",
        "tlit": "yastaṭīʿūna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتَطَعْتَ",
        "answer": "you can",
        "pcklId": "96",
        "tlit": "is'taṭaʿta",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "طُولًا",
        "answer": "(in) height",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ṭūlan",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "الطَّيِّبَاتِ",
        "answer": "the good things",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "l-ṭayibāti",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَائِرَهُ",
        "answer": "his fate",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "ṭāirahu",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "طِينًا",
        "answer": "(from) clay",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ṭīnan",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَظَلَمُوا",
        "answer": "but they wronged",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "faẓalamū",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُظْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "they will be wronged",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "yuẓ'lamūna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّالِمُونَ",
        "answer": "the wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "229",
        "tlit": "l-ẓālimūna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّالِمِينَ",
        "answer": "the wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "230",
        "tlit": "l-ẓālimīna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّالِمُونَ",
        "answer": "the wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "231",
        "tlit": "l-ẓālimūna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَظْلُومًا",
        "answer": "wrongfully",
        "pcklId": "312",
        "tlit": "maẓlūman",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَظُنُّونَ",
        "answer": "and you will think",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "wataẓunnūna",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَأَظُنُّكَ",
        "answer": "[I] think you ",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "la-aẓunnuka",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَأَظُنُّكَ",
        "answer": "[I] surely think you",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "la-aẓunnuka",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَهِيرًا",
        "answer": "assistants",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "ẓahīran",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْبُدُوا",
        "answer": "worship",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "taʿbudū",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِعَبْدِهِ",
        "answer": "His servant",
        "pcklId": "166",
        "tlit": "biʿabdihi",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَبْدًا",
        "answer": "a servant",
        "pcklId": "167",
        "tlit": "ʿabdan",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِبَادًا",
        "answer": "servants",
        "pcklId": "168",
        "tlit": "ʿibādan",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِبَادِهِ",
        "answer": "(of) His servants",
        "pcklId": "169",
        "tlit": "ʿibādihi",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِعِبَادِهِ",
        "answer": "of His slaves",
        "pcklId": "170",
        "tlit": "biʿibādihi",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِعِبَادِي",
        "answer": "to My slaves",
        "pcklId": "171",
        "tlit": "liʿibādī",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِبَادِي",
        "answer": "My slaves",
        "pcklId": "172",
        "tlit": "ʿibādī",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِعِبَادِهِ",
        "answer": "of His slaves",
        "pcklId": "173",
        "tlit": "biʿibādihi",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْتَدْنَا",
        "answer": "We have prepared",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "aʿtadnā",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَجَّلْنَا",
        "answer": "We hasten",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "ʿajjalnā",
        "frequency": "47",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَجُولًا",
        "answer": "ever hasty",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "ʿajūlan",
        "frequency": "47",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَاجِلَةَ",
        "answer": "the immediate",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "l-ʿājilata",
        "frequency": "47",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَدَدَ",
        "answer": "(the) number",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "ʿadada",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَدُوًّا",
        "answer": "an enemy",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "ʿaduwwan",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُعَذِّبْكُمْ",
        "answer": "He will punish you",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "yuʿadhib'kum",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابًا",
        "answer": "a punishment",
        "pcklId": "176",
        "tlit": "ʿadhāban",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابَهُ",
        "answer": "His punishment",
        "pcklId": "177",
        "tlit": "ʿadhābahu",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابَ",
        "answer": "(the) punishment",
        "pcklId": "178",
        "tlit": "ʿadhāba",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابًا",
        "answer": "with a punishment",
        "pcklId": "179",
        "tlit": "ʿadhāban",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُعَذِّبِينَ",
        "answer": "are to punish",
        "pcklId": "367",
        "tlit": "muʿadhibīna",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُعَذِّبُوهَا",
        "answer": "punish it",
        "pcklId": "368",
        "tlit": "muʿadhibūhā",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَرْشِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Throne",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "l-ʿarshi",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُعْرِضَنَّ",
        "answer": "you turn away",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "tuʿ'riḍanna",
        "frequency": "79",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْرَضْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you turn away",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "aʿraḍtum",
        "frequency": "79",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْرَضَ",
        "answer": "he turns away",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "aʿraḍa",
        "frequency": "79",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَسَىٰ",
        "answer": "(It) may be",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "ʿasā",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَسَىٰ",
        "answer": "Perhaps",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "ʿasā",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَسَىٰ",
        "answer": "it may be",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "ʿasā",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَطَاءِ",
        "answer": "(the) gift",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "ʿaṭāi",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَطَاءُ",
        "answer": "(the) gift",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "ʿaṭāu",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَظِيمًا",
        "answer": "grave",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "ʿaẓīman",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِظَامًا",
        "answer": "bones",
        "pcklId": "114",
        "tlit": "ʿiẓāman",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِظَامًا",
        "answer": "bones",
        "pcklId": "115",
        "tlit": "ʿiẓāman",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِتَعْلَمُوا",
        "answer": "and that you may know",
        "pcklId": "209",
        "tlit": "walitaʿlamū",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِمْتَ",
        "answer": "you have known",
        "pcklId": "210",
        "tlit": "ʿalim'ta",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "know best",
        "pcklId": "441",
        "tlit": "aʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "(is) most knowing",
        "pcklId": "464",
        "tlit": "aʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "(is) most knowing",
        "pcklId": "465",
        "tlit": "aʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "(is) most knowing",
        "pcklId": "466",
        "tlit": "aʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "(is) most knowing",
        "pcklId": "467",
        "tlit": "aʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِلْمٌ",
        "answer": "any knowledge",
        "pcklId": "595",
        "tlit": "ʿil'mun",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعِلْمِ",
        "answer": "the knowledge",
        "pcklId": "596",
        "tlit": "l-ʿil'mi",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعِلْمَ",
        "answer": "the knowledge",
        "pcklId": "597",
        "tlit": "l-ʿil'ma",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَتَعْلُنَّ",
        "answer": "and surely you will reach",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "walataʿlunna",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلَوْا",
        "answer": "they had conquered",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "ʿalaw",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَعَالَىٰ",
        "answer": "and Exalted is He",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "wataʿālā",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "عُلُوًّا",
        "answer": "haughtiness",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "ʿuluwwan",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "عُلُوًّا",
        "answer": "(by) height",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "ʿuluwwan",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "do",
        "pcklId": "113",
        "tlit": "yaʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْمَلُ",
        "answer": "works",
        "pcklId": "114",
        "tlit": "yaʿmalu",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْمَىٰ",
        "answer": "blind",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "aʿmā",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْمَىٰ",
        "answer": "(will be) blind",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "aʿmā",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "عُمْيًا",
        "answer": "blind",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "ʿum'yan",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعِنَبٍ",
        "answer": "and grapes",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "waʿinabin",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَكَ",
        "answer": "with you",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "ʿindaka",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَ",
        "answer": "near",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "ʿinda",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "عُنُقِهِ",
        "answer": "his neck",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ʿunuqihi",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "عُنُقِكَ",
        "answer": "your neck",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ʿunuqika",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْعَهْدِ",
        "answer": "the covenant",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "bil-ʿahdi",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَهْدَ",
        "answer": "the covenant",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "l-ʿahda",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "عُدْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you return",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "ʿudttum",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "عُدْنَا",
        "answer": "We will return",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "ʿud'nā",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُعِيدُنَا",
        "answer": "will restore us",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "yuʿīdunā",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُعِيدَكُمْ",
        "answer": "He will send you back",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "yuʿīdakum",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "غُرُورًا",
        "answer": "delusion",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "ghurūran",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيُغْرِقَكُمْ",
        "answer": "and drown you",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "fayugh'riqakum",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَغْرَقْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "but We drowned him",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "fa-aghraqnāhu",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَسَقِ",
        "answer": "(the) darkness",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ghasaqi",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَفُورًا",
        "answer": "Most Forgiving",
        "pcklId": "152",
        "tlit": "ghafūran",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَفُورًا",
        "answer": "Oft-Forgiving",
        "pcklId": "182",
        "tlit": "ghafūran",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَغْلُولَةً",
        "answer": "chained",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "maghlūlatan",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَيْرَهُ",
        "answer": "other (than) it",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "ghayrahu",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْفُؤَادَ",
        "answer": "and the heart",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "wal-fuāda",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتِيلًا",
        "answer": "(even as much as) a hair on a date seed",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "fatīlan",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيَفْتِنُونَكَ",
        "answer": "tempt you away",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "layaftinūnaka",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "فِتْنَةً",
        "answer": "(as) a trial",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "fit'natan",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَفْجُرَ",
        "answer": "you cause to gush forth",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "tafjura",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتُفَجِّرَ",
        "answer": "and cause to gush forth",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "fatufajjira",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفَجْرِ",
        "answer": "at dawn",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "l-fajri",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفَجْرِ",
        "answer": "(at) the dawn",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "l-fajri",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَفْجِيرًا",
        "answer": "abundantly",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "tafjīran",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاحِشَةً",
        "answer": "an immorality",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "fāḥishatan",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَرَقْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "We have divided",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "faraqnāhu",
        "frequency": "72",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِتَفْتَرِيَ",
        "answer": "that you invent",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "litaftariya",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاسْتَفْزِزْ",
        "answer": "And incite",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wa-is'tafziz",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيَسْتَفِزُّونَكَ",
        "answer": "(to) scare you",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "layastafizzūnaka",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَفِزَّهُمْ",
        "answer": "drive them out",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yastafizzahum",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَتُفْسِدُنَّ",
        "answer": "Surely you will cause corruption",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "latuf'sidunna",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَفَسَقُوا",
        "answer": "but they defiantly disobey",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "fafasaqū",
        "frequency": "54",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَصَّلْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "We have explained it",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "faṣṣalnāhu",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَفْصِيلًا",
        "answer": "(in) detail",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "tafṣīlan",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَضَّلْنَا",
        "answer": "We preferred",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "faḍḍalnā",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَضَّلْنَا",
        "answer": "We have preferred",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "faḍḍalnā",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَفَضَّلْنَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "and We preferred them",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "wafaḍḍalnāhum",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَضْلًا",
        "answer": "bounty",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "faḍlan",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَضْلِهِ",
        "answer": "His Bounty",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "faḍlihi",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَضْلَهُ",
        "answer": "His Bounty",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "faḍlahu",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَفْضِيلًا",
        "answer": "(in) excellence",
        "pcklId": "102",
        "tlit": "tafḍīlan",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَفْضِيلًا",
        "answer": "(with) preference",
        "pcklId": "103",
        "tlit": "tafḍīlan",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَطَرَكُمْ",
        "answer": "created you",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "faṭarakum",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَفْعُولًا",
        "answer": "fulfilled",
        "pcklId": "104",
        "tlit": "mafʿūlan",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَمَفْعُولًا",
        "answer": "surely fulfilled",
        "pcklId": "105",
        "tlit": "lamafʿūlan",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَفْقَهُونَ",
        "answer": "you understand",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "tafqahūna",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَفْقَهُوهُ",
        "answer": "they understand it",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "yafqahūhu",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفُلْكَ",
        "answer": "the ship",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "l-ful'ka",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِهِ",
        "answer": "before it",
        "pcklId": "132",
        "tlit": "qablihi",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلَ",
        "answer": "before",
        "pcklId": "237",
        "tlit": "qabla",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلَكَ",
        "answer": "before you",
        "pcklId": "238",
        "tlit": "qablaka",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبِيلًا",
        "answer": "before (us)",
        "pcklId": "287",
        "tlit": "qabīlan",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَتُورًا",
        "answer": "stingy",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "qatūran",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقْتُلُوا",
        "answer": "kill",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "taqtulū",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقْتُلُوا",
        "answer": "kill",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "taqtulū",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُتِلَ",
        "answer": "(is) killed",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "qutila",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَتْلَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their killing",
        "pcklId": "166",
        "tlit": "qatlahum",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَتْلِ",
        "answer": "the killing",
        "pcklId": "167",
        "tlit": "l-qatli",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَقْدِرُ",
        "answer": "and straitens",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "wayaqdiru",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَادِرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) Able",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "tlit": "qādirun",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "اقْرَأْ",
        "answer": "Read",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "iq'ra",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَرَأْتَ",
        "answer": "you recite",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "qarata",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقْرَءُونَ",
        "answer": "will read",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "yaqraūna",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَقْرَؤُهُ",
        "answer": "we could read it",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "naqra-uhu",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِتَقْرَأَهُ",
        "answer": "that you might recite it",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "litaqra-ahu",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقُرْآنَ",
        "answer": "the Quran",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "l-qur'āna",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقُرْآنِ",
        "answer": "the Quran",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "l-qur'āni",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقُرْآنَ",
        "answer": "the Quran",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "l-qur'āna",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقُرْآنِ",
        "answer": "the Quran",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "l-qur'āni",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقُرْآنِ",
        "answer": "the Quran",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "l-qur'āni",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقُرْآنَ",
        "answer": "and Quran",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "waqur'āna",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُرْآنَ",
        "answer": "the Quran",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "qur'āna",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقُرْآنِ",
        "answer": "the Quran",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "l-qur'āni",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقُرْآنِ",
        "answer": "Quran",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "l-qur'āni",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقُرْآنِ",
        "answer": "Quran",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "l-qur'āni",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقُرْآنًا",
        "answer": "And the Quran",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "waqur'ānan",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقْرَبُوا",
        "answer": "go near",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "taqrabū",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقْرَبُوا",
        "answer": "come near",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "taqrabū",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَقْرَبُ",
        "answer": "(is) nearest",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "aqrabu",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقُرْبَىٰ",
        "answer": "the relatives",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "l-qur'bā",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَرِيبًا",
        "answer": "soon",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "qarīban",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقُرُونِ",
        "answer": "the generations",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "l-qurūni",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَرْيَةً",
        "answer": "a town",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "qaryatan",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَرْيَةٍ",
        "answer": "town",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "qaryatin",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْقِسْطَاسِ",
        "answer": "with the balance",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "bil-qis'ṭāsi",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَاصِفًا",
        "answer": "a hurricane",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "qāṣifan",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَقْصَى",
        "answer": "Al-Masjid Al-Aqsa",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-aqṣā",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَضَيْنَا",
        "answer": "And We decreed",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "waqaḍaynā",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَضَىٰ",
        "answer": "And has decreed",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "waqaḍā",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَقْعُدَ",
        "answer": "lest you will sit",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "fataqʿuda",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَقْعُدَ",
        "answer": "so that you sit",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "fataqʿuda",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقْفُ",
        "answer": "pursue",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "taqfu",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلُوبِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their hearts",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "qulūbihim",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَلِيلًا",
        "answer": "a little (while)",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "qalīlan",
        "frequency": "76",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَلِيلًا",
        "answer": "a few",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "qalīlan",
        "frequency": "76",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَلِيلًا",
        "answer": "a little",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "qalīlan",
        "frequency": "76",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَلِيلًا",
        "answer": "a little",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "qalīlan",
        "frequency": "76",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَلِيلًا",
        "answer": "a little",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "qalīlan",
        "frequency": "76",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقُلْ",
        "answer": "say",
        "pcklId": "776",
        "tlit": "taqul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقُلْ",
        "answer": "but speak",
        "pcklId": "777",
        "tlit": "waqul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقُلْ",
        "answer": "and say",
        "pcklId": "778",
        "tlit": "waqul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَقُلْ",
        "answer": "then say",
        "pcklId": "779",
        "tlit": "faqul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَتَقُولُونَ",
        "answer": "surely say",
        "pcklId": "780",
        "tlit": "lataqūlūna",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "781",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُولُونَ",
        "answer": "they say",
        "pcklId": "782",
        "tlit": "yaqūlūna",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُولُونَ",
        "answer": "they say",
        "pcklId": "783",
        "tlit": "yaqūlūna",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُولُ",
        "answer": "say",
        "pcklId": "784",
        "tlit": "yaqūlu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالُوا",
        "answer": "And they say",
        "pcklId": "785",
        "tlit": "waqālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "786",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَسَيَقُولُونَ",
        "answer": "Then they will say",
        "pcklId": "787",
        "tlit": "fasayaqūlūna",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلِ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "788",
        "tlit": "quli",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَقُولُونَ",
        "answer": "and they say",
        "pcklId": "789",
        "tlit": "wayaqūlūna",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "790",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقُلْ",
        "answer": "And say",
        "pcklId": "791",
        "tlit": "waqul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُولُوا",
        "answer": "(to) say",
        "pcklId": "792",
        "tlit": "yaqūlū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلِ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "793",
        "tlit": "quli",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْنَا",
        "answer": "We said",
        "pcklId": "794",
        "tlit": "qul'nā",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْنَا",
        "answer": "We said",
        "pcklId": "795",
        "tlit": "qul'nā",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "796",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "797",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "798",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقُلْ",
        "answer": "And say",
        "pcklId": "799",
        "tlit": "waqul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقُلْ",
        "answer": "And say",
        "pcklId": "800",
        "tlit": "waqul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "801",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلِ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "802",
        "tlit": "quli",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "803",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالُوا",
        "answer": "And they say",
        "pcklId": "804",
        "tlit": "waqālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "805",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "they said",
        "pcklId": "806",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "807",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "808",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالُوا",
        "answer": "and said",
        "pcklId": "809",
        "tlit": "waqālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "810",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَقَالَ",
        "answer": "then said",
        "pcklId": "811",
        "tlit": "faqāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "812",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقُلْنَا",
        "answer": "And We said",
        "pcklId": "813",
        "tlit": "waqul'nā",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "814",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَقُولُونَ",
        "answer": "And they say",
        "pcklId": "815",
        "tlit": "wayaqūlūna",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلِ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "816",
        "tlit": "quli",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقُلِ",
        "answer": "And say",
        "pcklId": "817",
        "tlit": "waquli",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْلُ",
        "answer": "the word",
        "pcklId": "1658",
        "tlit": "l-qawlu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْلًا",
        "answer": "a word",
        "pcklId": "1659",
        "tlit": "qawlan",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْلًا",
        "answer": "a word",
        "pcklId": "1660",
        "tlit": "qawlan",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْلًا",
        "answer": "a word",
        "pcklId": "1661",
        "tlit": "qawlan",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَقِمِ",
        "answer": "Establish",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "aqimi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَقْوَمُ",
        "answer": "(is) most straight",
        "pcklId": "99",
        "tlit": "aqwamu",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقِيَامَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Resurrection",
        "pcklId": "518",
        "tlit": "l-qiyāmati",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقِيَامَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Resurrection",
        "pcklId": "519",
        "tlit": "l-qiyāmati",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقِيَامَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Resurrection",
        "pcklId": "520",
        "tlit": "l-qiyāmati",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقِيَامَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Resurrection",
        "pcklId": "521",
        "tlit": "l-qiyāmati",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَقَامًا",
        "answer": "(to) a station",
        "pcklId": "574",
        "tlit": "maqāman",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُسْتَقِيمِ",
        "answer": "the straight",
        "pcklId": "630",
        "tlit": "l-mus'taqīmi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكْبُرُ",
        "answer": "(is) great",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yakburu",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَبِّرْهُ",
        "answer": "And magnify Him",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "wakabbir'hu",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَكْبَرُ",
        "answer": "and greater",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "wa-akbaru",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَكْبَرُ",
        "answer": "(is) greater",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "akbaru",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِبَرَ",
        "answer": "the old age",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "l-kibara",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَبِيرًا",
        "answer": "great",
        "pcklId": "107",
        "tlit": "kabīran",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَبِيرًا",
        "answer": "great",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "tlit": "kabīran",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَبِيرًا",
        "answer": "great",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "tlit": "kabīran",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَبِيرًا",
        "answer": "great",
        "pcklId": "110",
        "tlit": "kabīran",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَبِيرًا",
        "answer": "great",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "tlit": "kabīran",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَبِيرًا",
        "answer": "great",
        "pcklId": "132",
        "tlit": "kabīran",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكْبِيرًا",
        "answer": "(with all) magnificence",
        "pcklId": "145",
        "tlit": "takbīran",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابَ",
        "answer": "the Book",
        "pcklId": "189",
        "tlit": "l-kitāba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابِ",
        "answer": "the Book",
        "pcklId": "190",
        "tlit": "l-kitābi",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "كِتَابًا",
        "answer": "a record",
        "pcklId": "191",
        "tlit": "kitāban",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "كِتَابَكَ",
        "answer": "your record",
        "pcklId": "192",
        "tlit": "kitābaka",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابِ",
        "answer": "the Book",
        "pcklId": "193",
        "tlit": "l-kitābi",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "كِتَابَهُ",
        "answer": "his record",
        "pcklId": "194",
        "tlit": "kitābahu",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "كِتَابَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their records",
        "pcklId": "195",
        "tlit": "kitābahum",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "كِتَابًا",
        "answer": "a book",
        "pcklId": "196",
        "tlit": "kitāban",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَكْثَرَ",
        "answer": "more",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "akthara",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَكْثَرُ",
        "answer": "most",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "aktharu",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَثِيرٍ",
        "answer": "many",
        "pcklId": "116",
        "tlit": "kathīrin",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذَّبَ",
        "answer": "denied",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "kadhaba",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَرَّةَ",
        "answer": "the return victory",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-karata",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَرَّمْتَ",
        "answer": "You have honored",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "karramta",
        "frequency": "47",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَرَّمْنَا",
        "answer": "We have honored",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "karramnā",
        "frequency": "47",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَرِيمًا",
        "answer": "noble",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "karīman",
        "frequency": "47",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَكْرُوهًا",
        "answer": "hateful",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "makrūhan",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "كِسَفًا",
        "answer": "(in) pieces",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "kisafan",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَشْفَ",
        "answer": "(to) remove",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "kashfa",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you disbelieved",
        "pcklId": "150",
        "tlit": "kafartum",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieved",
        "pcklId": "151",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفُورًا",
        "answer": "ungrateful",
        "pcklId": "379",
        "tlit": "kafūran",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفُورًا",
        "answer": "ungrateful",
        "pcklId": "386",
        "tlit": "kafūran",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُفُورًا",
        "answer": "disbelief",
        "pcklId": "391",
        "tlit": "kufūran",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُفُورًا",
        "answer": "disbelief",
        "pcklId": "392",
        "tlit": "kufūran",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْكَافِرِينَ",
        "answer": "for the disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "452",
        "tlit": "lil'kāfirīna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَىٰ",
        "answer": "Sufficient",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "kafā",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَفَىٰ",
        "answer": "And sufficient",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "wakafā",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَفَىٰ",
        "answer": "And sufficient",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "wakafā",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَىٰ",
        "answer": "Sufficient is",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "kafā",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكُلَّ",
        "answer": "And every",
        "pcklId": "155",
        "tlit": "wakulla",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكُلَّ",
        "answer": "And (for) every",
        "pcklId": "156",
        "tlit": "wakulla",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلًّا",
        "answer": "(To) each",
        "pcklId": "157",
        "tlit": "kullan",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلَّ",
        "answer": "(to its) utmost",
        "pcklId": "158",
        "tlit": "kulla",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلُّ",
        "answer": "all",
        "pcklId": "159",
        "tlit": "kullu",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلُّ",
        "answer": "All",
        "pcklId": "160",
        "tlit": "kullu",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلَّ",
        "answer": "all",
        "pcklId": "161",
        "tlit": "kulla",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلٌّ",
        "answer": "Each",
        "pcklId": "162",
        "tlit": "kullun",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "163",
        "tlit": "kulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلَّمَا",
        "answer": "every time",
        "pcklId": "372",
        "tlit": "kullamā",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "كِلَاهُمَا",
        "answer": "both of them",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "kilāhumā",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَكِنَّةً",
        "answer": "coverings",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "akinnatan",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَادُوا",
        "answer": "they were about (to)",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "kādū",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "كِدْتَ",
        "answer": "you almost",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "kidtta",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَادُوا",
        "answer": "they were about",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "kādū",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "was",
        "pcklId": "639",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَانَ",
        "answer": "and (it) was",
        "pcklId": "640",
        "tlit": "wakāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَانَ",
        "answer": "And is",
        "pcklId": "641",
        "tlit": "wakāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنَّا",
        "answer": "We",
        "pcklId": "642",
        "tlit": "kunnā",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "should",
        "pcklId": "643",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "[are]",
        "pcklId": "644",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "is",
        "pcklId": "645",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكُونُوا",
        "answer": "you are",
        "pcklId": "646",
        "tlit": "takūnū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "is",
        "pcklId": "647",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "are",
        "pcklId": "648",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَانَ",
        "answer": "And is",
        "pcklId": "649",
        "tlit": "wakāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "is",
        "pcklId": "650",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "is",
        "pcklId": "651",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "is",
        "pcklId": "652",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "is",
        "pcklId": "653",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "will be",
        "pcklId": "654",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "will be",
        "pcklId": "655",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "is",
        "pcklId": "656",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "(there) were",
        "pcklId": "657",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "is",
        "pcklId": "658",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنَّا",
        "answer": "we are",
        "pcklId": "659",
        "tlit": "kunnā",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُونُوا",
        "answer": "Be",
        "pcklId": "660",
        "tlit": "kūnū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكُونَ",
        "answer": "(it) will be",
        "pcklId": "661",
        "tlit": "yakūna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "is",
        "pcklId": "662",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "is",
        "pcklId": "663",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "That is",
        "pcklId": "664",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "is",
        "pcklId": "665",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَانَ",
        "answer": "And is",
        "pcklId": "666",
        "tlit": "wakāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "is",
        "pcklId": "667",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "is",
        "pcklId": "668",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "is",
        "pcklId": "669",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "he is",
        "pcklId": "670",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "is",
        "pcklId": "671",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "were",
        "pcklId": "672",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكُونَ",
        "answer": "you have",
        "pcklId": "673",
        "tlit": "takūna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكُونَ",
        "answer": "is",
        "pcklId": "674",
        "tlit": "yakūna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُ",
        "answer": "am I",
        "pcklId": "675",
        "tlit": "kuntu",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "(there) were",
        "pcklId": "676",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "is",
        "pcklId": "677",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنَّا",
        "answer": "we are",
        "pcklId": "678",
        "tlit": "kunnā",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَانَ",
        "answer": "And is",
        "pcklId": "679",
        "tlit": "wakāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "is",
        "pcklId": "680",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكُنْ",
        "answer": "is",
        "pcklId": "681",
        "tlit": "yakun",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكُنْ",
        "answer": "is",
        "pcklId": "682",
        "tlit": "yakun",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَيْفَ",
        "answer": "how",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "kayfa",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَيْفَ",
        "answer": "how",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "kayfa",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "كِلْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you measure",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "kil'tum",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَيْلَ",
        "answer": "[the] measure",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "l-kayla",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَبِثْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you had remained",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "labith'tum",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَلْبَثُونَ",
        "answer": "they (would) have stayed",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "yalbathūna",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَدُنْكَ",
        "answer": "near You",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "ladunka",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلْزَمْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "We have fastened to him",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "alzamnāhu",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَلْعُونَةَ",
        "answer": "the accursed",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "l-malʿūnata",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَفِيفًا",
        "answer": "(as) a mixed crowd",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "lafīfan",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَلْقَاهُ",
        "answer": "which he will find",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "yalqāhu",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتُلْقَىٰ",
        "answer": "lest you should be thrown",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "fatul'qā",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَلُومًا",
        "answer": "blameworthy",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "malūman",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَلُومًا",
        "answer": "blameworthy",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "malūman",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيْسَ",
        "answer": "not",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "laysa",
        "frequency": "89",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيْسَ",
        "answer": "not",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "laysa",
        "frequency": "89",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيْلًا",
        "answer": "(by) night",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "laylan",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّيْلَ",
        "answer": "the night",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "al-layla",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّيْلِ",
        "answer": "(of) the night",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "al-layli",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّيْلِ",
        "answer": "(of) the night",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "al-layli",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّيْلِ",
        "answer": "the night",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "al-layli",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِمِثْلِ",
        "answer": "the like",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "bimith'li",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِمِثْلِهِ",
        "answer": "the like of it",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "bimith'lihi",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِثْلَهُمْ",
        "answer": "the like of them",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "mith'lahum",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَمْثَالَ",
        "answer": "the examples",
        "pcklId": "119",
        "tlit": "l-amthāla",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَثَلٍ",
        "answer": "example",
        "pcklId": "120",
        "tlit": "mathalin",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَمَحَوْنَا",
        "answer": "Then We erased",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "famaḥawnā",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَمْدَدْنَاكُمْ",
        "answer": "And We reinforced you",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "wa-amdadnākum",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُمِدُّ",
        "answer": "We extend",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "numiddu",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرَحًا",
        "answer": "(with) insolence",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "maraḥan",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرَّتَيْنِ",
        "answer": "twice",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "marratayni",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرَّةٍ",
        "answer": "time",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "marratin",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرَّةٍ",
        "answer": "time",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "marratin",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَسَّكُمُ",
        "answer": "touches you",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "massakumu",
        "frequency": "61",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَسَّهُ",
        "answer": "touches him",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "massahu",
        "frequency": "61",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَأَمْسَكْتُمْ",
        "answer": "surely you would withhold",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "la-amsaktum",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَمْشِ",
        "answer": "walk",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "tamshi",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَمْشُونَ",
        "answer": "walking",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "yamshūna",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُكْثٍ",
        "answer": "intervals",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "muk'thin",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِمْلَاقٍ",
        "answer": "(of) poverty",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "im'lāqin",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَمْلِكُونَ",
        "answer": "they have power",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "yamlikūna",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَمْلِكُونَ",
        "answer": "possess",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "tamlikūna",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُلْكِ",
        "answer": "the dominion",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "l-mul'ki",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَلَائِكَةِ",
        "answer": "the Angels",
        "pcklId": "157",
        "tlit": "l-malāikati",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْمَلَائِكَةِ",
        "answer": "to the Angels",
        "pcklId": "158",
        "tlit": "lil'malāikati",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمَلَائِكَةِ",
        "answer": "and the Angels",
        "pcklId": "159",
        "tlit": "wal-malāikati",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَلَائِكَةٌ",
        "answer": "Angels",
        "pcklId": "160",
        "tlit": "malāikatun",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَلَكًا",
        "answer": "an Angel",
        "pcklId": "161",
        "tlit": "malakan",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَنَعَنَا",
        "answer": "stopped Us",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "manaʿanā",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَنَعَ",
        "answer": "prevented",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "manaʿa",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَمَاتِ",
        "answer": "(after) the death",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "l-mamāti",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِأَمْوَالٍ",
        "answer": "with the wealth",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "bi-amwālin",
        "frequency": "86",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَالَ",
        "answer": "(the) wealth",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "māla",
        "frequency": "86",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَمْوَالِ",
        "answer": "the wealth",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "l-amwāli",
        "frequency": "86",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَأَىٰ",
        "answer": "and becomes remote",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wanaā",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّبِيِّينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the Prophets",
        "pcklId": "121",
        "tlit": "l-nabiyīna",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْبُوعًا",
        "answer": "a spring",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yanbūʿan",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَجَّاكُمْ",
        "answer": "He delivers you",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "najjākum",
        "frequency": "84",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَجْوَىٰ",
        "answer": "(are) in private conversation",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "najwā",
        "frequency": "84",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَخِيلٍ",
        "answer": "date-palms",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "nakhīlin",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَذِيرًا",
        "answer": "and a warner",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "wanadhīran",
        "frequency": "130",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْزَغُ",
        "answer": "sows discord",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yanzaghu",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَزَلَ",
        "answer": "it descended",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "nazala",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنُنَزِّلُ",
        "answer": "And We reveal",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "wanunazzilu",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُنَزِّلَ",
        "answer": "you bring down",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "tunazzila",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَنَزَّلْنَا",
        "answer": "surely We (would) have sent down",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "lanazzalnā",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَزَّلْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "And We have revealed it",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "wanazzalnāhu",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْزَلَ",
        "answer": "has sent down",
        "pcklId": "182",
        "tlit": "anzala",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْزَلْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "We sent it down",
        "pcklId": "183",
        "tlit": "anzalnāhu",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَنْزِيلًا",
        "answer": "(in) stages",
        "pcklId": "269",
        "tlit": "tanzīlan",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَنْشُورًا",
        "answer": "wide open",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "manshūran",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَصِيرًا",
        "answer": "any helper",
        "pcklId": "125",
        "tlit": "naṣīran",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَصِيرًا",
        "answer": "helping",
        "pcklId": "140",
        "tlit": "naṣīran",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَنْصُورًا",
        "answer": "helped",
        "pcklId": "152",
        "tlit": "manṣūran",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "انْظُرْ",
        "answer": "See",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "unẓur",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "انْظُرْ",
        "answer": "See",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "unẓur",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْعَمْنَا",
        "answer": "We bestow favor",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "anʿamnā",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَسَيُنْغِضُونَ",
        "answer": "Then they will shake",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "fasayun'ghiḍūna",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُفُورًا",
        "answer": "(in) aversion",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "nufūran",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُفُورًا",
        "answer": "(in) aversion",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "nufūran",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفِيرًا",
        "answer": "numerous",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "nafīran",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِأَنْفُسِكُمْ",
        "answer": "for yourselves",
        "pcklId": "179",
        "tlit": "li-anfusikum",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِنَفْسِكَ",
        "answer": "(is) yourself",
        "pcklId": "180",
        "tlit": "binafsika",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِنَفْسِهِ",
        "answer": "for his soul",
        "pcklId": "181",
        "tlit": "linafsihi",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُفُوسِكُمْ",
        "answer": "yourselves",
        "pcklId": "182",
        "tlit": "nufūsikum",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّفْسَ",
        "answer": "the soul",
        "pcklId": "183",
        "tlit": "l-nafsa",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْإِنْفَاقِ",
        "answer": "(of) spending",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "tlit": "l-infāqi",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَافِلَةً",
        "answer": "(as) additional",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "nāfilatan",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَنْهَرْهُمَا",
        "answer": "repel them",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "tanharhumā",
        "frequency": "113",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالنَّهَارَ",
        "answer": "and the day",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "wal-nahāra",
        "frequency": "113",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّهَارِ",
        "answer": "(of) the day",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "l-nahāri",
        "frequency": "113",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَنْهَارَ",
        "answer": "the rivers",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "l-anhāra",
        "frequency": "113",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالنَّاسِ",
        "answer": "the mankind",
        "pcklId": "139",
        "tlit": "bil-nāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلنَّاسِ",
        "answer": "for mankind",
        "pcklId": "140",
        "tlit": "lilnnāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلنَّاسِ",
        "answer": "to mankind",
        "pcklId": "141",
        "tlit": "lilnnāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسِ",
        "answer": "(of) the mankind",
        "pcklId": "142",
        "tlit": "l-nāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسَ",
        "answer": "the people",
        "pcklId": "143",
        "tlit": "l-nāsa",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسِ",
        "answer": "the people",
        "pcklId": "144",
        "tlit": "l-nāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاقَةَ",
        "answer": "the she-camel",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "l-nāqata",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَهَجَّدْ",
        "answer": "arise from sleep for prayer",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "fatahajjad",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَهْدِي",
        "answer": "guides",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "yahdī",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَهْدِ",
        "answer": "Allah guides",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "yahdi",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "اهْتَدَىٰ",
        "answer": "(is) guided",
        "pcklId": "162",
        "tlit": "ih'tadā",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَهْتَدِي",
        "answer": "he is guided",
        "pcklId": "163",
        "tlit": "yahtadī",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْدَىٰ",
        "answer": "(is) best guided",
        "pcklId": "186",
        "tlit": "ahdā",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "هُدًى",
        "answer": "a guidance",
        "pcklId": "241",
        "tlit": "hudan",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْهُدَىٰ",
        "answer": "the guidance",
        "pcklId": "242",
        "tlit": "l-hudā",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُهْتَدِ",
        "answer": "the guided one",
        "pcklId": "295",
        "tlit": "l-muh'tadi",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُهْلِكَ",
        "answer": "We destroy",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "nuh'lika",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلَكْنَا",
        "answer": "We destroyed",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "ahlaknā",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُهْلِكُوهَا",
        "answer": "(will) destroy it",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "muh'likūhā",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَجِدُوا",
        "answer": "you will find",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "tajidū",
        "frequency": "107",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَجِدُوا",
        "answer": "you will find",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "tajidū",
        "frequency": "107",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَجِدُ",
        "answer": "you (would) have found",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "tajidu",
        "frequency": "107",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَجِدُ",
        "answer": "you will find",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "tajidu",
        "frequency": "107",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَجِدُ",
        "answer": "you would find",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "tajidu",
        "frequency": "107",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَجِدَ",
        "answer": "you will find",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "tajida",
        "frequency": "107",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "وُجُوهَكُمْ",
        "answer": "your faces",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "wujūhakum",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "وُجُوهِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their faces ",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "wujūhihim",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَحْدَهُ",
        "answer": "Alone",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "waḥdahu",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوْحَىٰ",
        "answer": "(was) revealed",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "awḥā",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوْحَيْنَا",
        "answer": "We revealed",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "awḥaynā",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوْحَيْنَا",
        "answer": "We have revealed",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "awḥaynā",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَزِرُ",
        "answer": "will bear",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "taziru",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "وِزْرَ",
        "answer": "burden",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "wiz'ra",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَازِرَةٌ",
        "answer": "a bearer of burden",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "wāziratun",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَزِنُوا",
        "answer": "and weigh",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wazinū",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْوَسِيلَةَ",
        "answer": "the means of access",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-wasīlata",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعِدْهُمْ",
        "answer": "and promise them",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "waʿid'hum",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعِدُهُمُ",
        "answer": "promises them",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "yaʿiduhumu",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعْدُ",
        "answer": "(the) promise",
        "pcklId": "107",
        "tlit": "waʿdu",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعْدًا",
        "answer": "a promise",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "tlit": "waʿdan",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعْدُ",
        "answer": "promise",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "tlit": "waʿdu",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعْدُ",
        "answer": "(the) promise",
        "pcklId": "110",
        "tlit": "waʿdu",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعْدُ",
        "answer": "(the) promise",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "tlit": "waʿdu",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَوْفُورًا",
        "answer": "ample",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "mawfūran",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَوْفُوا",
        "answer": "And fulfil",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "wa-awfū",
        "frequency": "66",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَوْفُوا",
        "answer": "And give full",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "wa-awfū",
        "frequency": "66",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقْرًا",
        "answer": "deafness",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "waqran",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكِيلًا",
        "answer": "(as) a Disposer of affairs",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "wakīlan",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكِيلًا",
        "answer": "(as) a guardian",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "wakīlan",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكِيلًا",
        "answer": "(as) a Guardian",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "wakīlan",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكِيلًا",
        "answer": "a guardian",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "wakīlan",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكِيلًا",
        "answer": "any advocate",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "wakīlan",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبِالْوَالِدَيْنِ",
        "answer": "and to the parents",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "wabil-wālidayni",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوْلَادَكُمْ",
        "answer": "your children",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "awlādakum",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَوْلَادِ",
        "answer": "and the children",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "wal-awlādi",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَدًا",
        "answer": "a son",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "waladan",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَّوْا",
        "answer": "they turn",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "wallaw",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِوَلِيِّهِ",
        "answer": "for his heir",
        "pcklId": "194",
        "tlit": "liwaliyyihi",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوْلِيَاءَ",
        "answer": "protectors",
        "pcklId": "195",
        "tlit": "awliyāa",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِيٌّ",
        "answer": "any protector",
        "pcklId": "196",
        "tlit": "waliyyun",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَئُوسًا",
        "answer": "(in) despair",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "yaūsan",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْيَتِيمِ",
        "answer": "(of) the orphan",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "l-yatīmi",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَدَكَ",
        "answer": "your hand",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "yadaka",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَيْسُورًا",
        "answer": "gentle",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "maysūran",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِيَمِينِهِ",
        "answer": "in his right hand",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "biyamīnihi",
        "frequency": "71",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمَ",
        "answer": "(on the) Day",
        "pcklId": "104",
        "tlit": "yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْيَوْمَ",
        "answer": "today",
        "pcklId": "105",
        "tlit": "l-yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمَ",
        "answer": "(On) the Day",
        "pcklId": "106",
        "tlit": "yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمِ",
        "answer": "(the) Day",
        "pcklId": "107",
        "tlit": "yawmi",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمِ",
        "answer": "(the) Day",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "tlit": "yawmi",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمَ",
        "answer": "(The) Day",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "tlit": "yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمَ",
        "answer": "(on) the Day",
        "pcklId": "110",
        "tlit": "yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "17",
        "ayah": "97"
    }
]; 
export default words;